[
    {
        "Question": "What was the name of lucille ball's character on i love lucy?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:What was the name of lucille ball's character on i love lucy?\n\nThought: First step is to generate the SPARQL query.\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: What was the name of lucille ball's character on i love lucy?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ ?x1 wdt:P31 <P1441:fictional_character> . ?x1 p:P674 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P674 wd:Q181943 . FILTER (wd:Q202444 = <P1705:name>) . }}\nThought:A query was generated. To verify whether the query is indeed correct, it should be executed on Wikidata.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ ?x1 wdt:P31 . ?x1 p:P674 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P674 wd:Q181943 . FILTER (wd:Q202444 = ) . }}\n\nObservation: That query failed. Perhaps you could try a different one? Maybe check the syntax, maybe double quotes etc!\nThought:The query constructed seems to be incomplete, and P161: character role might be the correct property rather than P674: characters. \n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q181943 p:P161 ?x2. ?x2 ps:P161 wd:Q209662; pq:P453 ?x1.}}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q17379228'}}]\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels. Now will get the Label\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q17379228]\n\nObservation: ['Lucy']\nFinal Answer:  Wikidata_Answer: [Lucy]\n\nAssistant Response: Lucy was the name of lucille ball's character on i love lucy"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was the narrator of the novel moby-dick ?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:Who was the narrator of the novel moby-dick ?\n\n\nThought:As the first step, need to generate the SPARQL query to query over Wikidata.\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: Who was the narrator of the novel moby-dick ?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ ?x1 wdt:P31 wd:Q5 . VALUES ?x2 {{ wd:Q174596 }} . ?x2 wdt:P31 wd:Q7725634 . ?x2 p:P1440 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:P1440 ?x1 . }}\nThought:The query now needs to be executed over Wikidata\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ ?x1 wdt:P31 wd:Q5 . VALUES ?x2 {{ wd:Q174596 }} . ?x2 wdt:P31 wd:Q7725634 . ?x2 p:P1440 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:P1440 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: The result is empty set possible reasons\n 1) The tool gave out improper sparql query \n2) The entity id used for constrution might be wrong \n3) Our LLM created its own query which is synctactically correct but the kg structure doesnt match the query\n                      For cases 1 and 3 you cant do much but for case 2 you can try to either change the entity id which gaves same answer from wikipedia.\nThought:Seems like the query execution gave empty results. By reconstructing the query, by using the property P2438: narratory, the query can be executed.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q174596 wdt:P2438 ?x1.}}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q6080485'}}]\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels. Now will get the Label\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: ['Q6080485']\n\nObservation: ['Ishmael']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [Ishmael]\n\nAssistant Response: Ishmael is the narrator of the novel moby-dick."
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the central theme of the breaking bad television series?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tWikiSearchSummary\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:What is the central theme of the breaking bad television series?\n\nThought:For answering the question, need to first generate the SPARQL query.\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: What is the central theme of the breaking bad television series?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q1079 p:P921 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P921 ?x1 . }}\nThought:This query needs to be executed to find the answer.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q1079 p:P921 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P921 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q844924'}}, {{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q906343'}}]\nThought:The answer is in QID, need to transform into a readable label.\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q844924,Q906343]\n\nObservation: ['drug trafficking', 'dysfunctional family']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [drug trafficking,dysfunctional family]\n\nAssistant Response: According to Wikidata, the central theme of breaking bad television series is drug trafficking,dysfunctional family."
    },
    {
        "Question": "When was the author of mirrorshades born?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tWikiSearch\tWikiSearch",
        "One_Shot": "Question:When was the author of mirrorshades born?\n\nThought:First, need to generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: When was the author of mirrorshades born?\n\nObservation: The possible reason is\n 1) The query is syntactically wrong\n\nThought:The query was not correct, so the query generator did not succeed. In a next step, a different query should be generated.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q2085020 p:P50 ?x4 . ?x4 ps:P50 ?x2 . ?x2 p:P569 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:P569 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': '1954-04-14T00:00:00Z'}}]\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [1954-04-14]\n\nAssistant Response: Editor of the Mirrorshades was born in 1954-04-14."
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the release year of game of thrones?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tRunSparql\tRunSparql",
        "One_Shot": "Question:What is the release year of game of thrones?\n\nThought:Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: What is the release year of game of thrones?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q23572 p:P577 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:P577 ?x2 . BIND (year(?x2) AS ?x1) . }}\nThought: Need to next execute the query over wikidata\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q23572 p:P577 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:P577 ?x2 . BIND (year(?x2) AS ?x1) . }}\n\nObservation: The result is empty set possible reasons\n 1) The tool gave out improper sparql query \n2) The entity id used for construction might be wrong \n3) Our LLM created its own query which is syntactically correct but the kg structure does not match the query\n                  \tFor cases 1 and 3 you cant do much but for case 2 you can try to either change the entity id which gives same answer from wikipedia.\nThought:The above query did not produce any result may be constructing query in different way might help\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q23572 wdt:P577 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: The result is empty set possible reasons\n 1) The tool gave out improper sparql query \n2) The entity id used for construction might be wrong \n3) Our LLM created its own query which is syntactically correct but the kg structure does not match the query\n                  \tFor cases 1 and 3 you cant do much but for case 2 you can try to either change the entity id which gives same answer from wikipedia.\nThought:The above query was wrong because of improper relation. Hence correcting the property to P580. Running the query again to execute on Wikidata\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q23572 wdt:P580 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': '2011-04-17T00:00:00Z'}}]\nFinal Answer:  Wikidata_Answer: [\"2011-04-17T00:00:00Z\"]\n\nAssistant Response: According to the Wikidata, release year of game of thrones is 2011."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who directed raiders of the lost ark?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:Who directed raiders of the lost ark?\n\nThought:Need to first generate the SPARQL queryAction:WikiSearch\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: Who directed raiders of the lost ark?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q174284 p:P57 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P57 ?x1 . }}\nThought:To find the answer to the question the query needs to be executed over Wikidata.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q174284 p:P57 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P57 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q8877'}}]\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels. Now will get the Label\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q8877]\n\nObservation: ['Steven Spielberg']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [Steven Spielberg]\n\nAssistant Response: Steven Spielberg directed raiders of the lost ark."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was the creator of sherlock holmes?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:Who was the creator of sherlock holmes?\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: Who was the creator of sherlock holmes?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ ?x1 wdt:P31 wd:Q5 . ?x1 p:P170 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P170 wd:Q4653 . }}\nThought:Run the generate SPARQL query\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ ?x1 wdt:P31 wd:Q5 . ?x1 p:P170 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P170 wd:Q4653 . }}\n\nObservation: The result is empty set possible reasons\n 1) The tool gave out improper sparql query \n2) The entity id used for constrution might be wrong \n3) Our LLM created its own query which is synctactical>\n                      For cases 1 and 3 you cant do much but for case 2 you can try to either change the entity id which gaves same answer from wikipedia.\nThought:The previous run was not successful. Trying to rewrite the query\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT ? x1 WHERE {{ wd: Q4653 wdt: P170 ? x1.}}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q35610'}}]\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels. Now will get the Label\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q35610]\n\nObservation: ['Arthur Conan Doyle']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [Arthur Conan Doyle]\n\nAssistant Response: Arthur Conan Doyle was the creator of Sherlock Holmes."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Creator of the the wheel of time?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:Creator of the the wheel of time?\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: Creator of the the wheel of time?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q4470 p:P170 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P170 ?x1 . }}\nThought:Run the SPARQL query\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q4470 p:P170 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P170 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: The result is empty set possible reasons\n 1) The tool gave out improper sparql query \n2) The entity id used for construction might be wrong \n3) Our LLM created its own query which is syntactic>\n  For cases 1 and 3 you cant do much but for case 2 you can try to either change the entity id which gives same answer from wikipedia.\nThought:The query above didn't return any result. Lets try to construct query in another way.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q4470 wdt:P50 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q166351'}}, {{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q457608'}}]\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels. Now will get the Label\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q166351,Q457608]\n\nObservation: ['Robert Jordan', 'Brandon Sanderson']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [Robert Jordan, Brandon Sanderson]\n\nAssistant Response: Robert Jordan, Brandon Sanderson are the creators of Wheel of Time."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who wrote the immortals of meluha?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:Who wrote the immortals of meluha?\n\nThought:Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: Who wrote the immortals of meluha?\n\nObservation: The possible reason is\n 1) The query is syntactically wrong\n\nThought:The above tool GenerateSparql did not return any query. Let's try to construct the query in another way .\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q6488199 wdt:P50 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: {{'value': 'http: //www.wikidata.org/entity/Q3661856'}}\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels. Now will get the Label\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q3661856]\n\nObservation: ['Amish Tripathi']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [Amish Tripathi]\n\nAssistant Response: According to Wikidata, Amish Tripathi wrote the immortals of meluha."
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the original language of the movie lord of the rings?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tWikiSearchSummary\tWikiSearchSummary\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:What is the original language of the movie lord of the rings?\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: What is the original language of the movie lord of the rings?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q190214 p:P364 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P364 ?x1 . }}\nThought:To find the answer to the question the query needs to be executed over Wikidata.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q190214 p:P364 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P364 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q1860'}}]\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels. Now will get the Label\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: ['Q1860']\n\nObservation: ['English']\nFinal Answer:  Wikidata_Answer: [English]\n\nAssistant Response: Original language of lord of the rings is English."
    },
    {
        "Question": "What was the narrative location of the book \"wuthering heights \"?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:What was the narrative location of the book \"wuthering heights \"?\n\n\nThought:Let's try to get information about the book \"wuthering heights \"\n\nAction:WikiSearch\n\nAction Input: wuthering heights\n\nObservation: Page: Wuthering Heights\nSummary: Wuthering Heights is an 1847 novel by Emily Brontë, set on the West Yorkshire moors. It revolves around two families, the Earnshaws and the Lintons, and their turbulent relationships with the Earnshaws' foster son, Heathcliff. The novel was influenced by Romanticism and Gothic fiction and is now considered one of the greatest novels ever written in English.\nThought:WikiSearch gave the necessary information and  found the answer on Wikipedia. It is West Yorkshire moors, which is in Northern England. Next step is to construct the query. First need to find the QID for Wuthering Heights.\n\nAction:GetWikidataID\n\nAction Input: Wuthering Heights\n\nObservation: ['Q202975']\nThought:The next step is to generate SPARQL query for the QID of Wuthering Heights.\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: Q202975\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q202975 p:P840 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P840 ?x1 . }}\nThought:To find the answer to the question the query needs to be executed over Wikidata\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q202975 p:P840 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P840 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q163'}}]\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels. Now will get the Label.\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q163]\n\nObservation: ['Yorkshire']\nFinal Answer: Wikipedia_Answer:West Yorkshire moors, Wikidata_Answer: [Yorkshire]\n\nAssistant Response: According to the Wikipedia article, Wuthering Heights is an 1847 novel by Emily Brontë, set on the West Yorkshire moors in Northern England. The entity page of  Wuthering Heights returns Yorkshire."
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the position played by franz beckenbauer?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:What is the position played by franz beckenbauer?\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: What is the position played by franz beckenbauer?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q4457 p:P413 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P413 ?x1 . }}\nThought:To get the result, the SPARQL query needs to be executed over Wikidata. wikidata\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q4457 p:P413 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P413 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q193592'}}, {{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q336286'}}, {{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q1489923'}}]\nThought:The response contains the Q-IDs. To get a natural language response, they need to be turned into labels.\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q193592,Q336286,Q1489923]\n\nObservation: ['midfielder', 'defender', 'sweeper']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [midfielder,defender,sweeper]\n\nAssistant Response: According to Wikidata, franz beckenbauer played as midfielder, defender and sweeper."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who created the riverdale television series?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tWikiSearchSummary\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:Who created the riverdale television series?\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: Who created the riverdale television series?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q23001951 p:P170 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P170 ?x1 . }}\nThought:To find the answer to the question the query needs to be executed over Wikidata.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q23001951 p:P170 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P170 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q7351575'}}]\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels.\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q7351575]\n\nObservation: ['Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa]\n\nAssistant Response: Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa created the riverdale television series."
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the total number of emmy awards received by amy sherman-palladino?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGetWikidataID\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql",
        "One_Shot": "Question:What is the total number of emmy awards received by amy sherman-palladino?\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: What is the total number of emmy awards received by amy sherman-palladino?\n\nObservation: The possible reason is\n 1) The query is syntactically wrong\n\nThought:This query might require P166: award received which are P361: part of Primetime Emmy Award \n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT (COUNT(?x1) AS ?x2) WHERE {{wd:Q436780 wdt:P166 ?x1 . ?x1 wdt:P361+ wd:Q1044427 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': '2'}}]\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [2]\n\nAssistant Response: Amy Sherman-Palladino received 2 emmy awards in total."
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the country of origin of the tv series coupling?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tWikiSearch\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:What is the country of origin of the tv series coupling?\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: What is the country of origin of the tv series coupling?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ ?x2 wdt:P31 wd:Q1197699 . ?x2 p:Q3373417 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:Q3373417 ?x1 . }}\nThought:Running the obtained SPARQL query.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ ?x2 wdt:P31 wd:Q1197699 . ?x2 p:Q3373417 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:Q3373417 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: The result is empty set possible reasons\n 1) The tool gave out improper SPARQL query \n 2) The entity id used for construction might be wrong \n 3) Our LLM created its own query which is syntactically correct but the kg structure does not match the query\n For cases 1 and 3 is is difficult to recover generally, but for case 2 you can try to either change the entity id which gives same answer from wikipedia.\nThought:For the above constructed SPARQL query, the entities and the relations picked are incorrect. The query requires the generated QID, Q944517 and the property might be P495: country of origin instead of Q3373417: country of origin. \n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT ?x1 ?x2 WHERE {{ wd:Q1137587 wdt:P495 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q145'}}]\nThought:The given Query outputs the QID. This QID needs to be converted into natural language label\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q145]\n\nObservation: ['United Kingdom']\nFinal Answer:  Wikidata_Answer: [United Kingdom]\n\nAssistant Response: Country of origin of the TV series coupling is United Kingdom."
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many seasons of the emily in paris series?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tWikiSearchSummary\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tRunSparql",
        "One_Shot": "Question:How many seasons of the emily in paris series?\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: How many seasons of the emily in paris series?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT  (COUNT(DISTINCT ?x2) AS ?x1) WHERE {{ ?x2 wdt:P31 wd:Q2490839 . ?x2 p:P179 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:P179 wd:Q64584978 . }}\nThought:Got the query and executing against wikidata now.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT (COUNT(DISTINCT ?x2) AS ?x1) WHERE {{ ?x2 wdt:P31 wd:Q2490839 . ?x2 p:P179 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:P179 wd:Q64584978 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': '0'}}]\nThought:The above query gives answer 0, which might be incorrect. As an alternative, P2437: number of seasons might be the correct property for this SPARQL construction. \n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q64584978 wdt:P2437 ?x1 .}}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': '3'}}]\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [3]\n\nAssistant Response: According to Wikidata, there are 3 seasons of emily in paris series."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was the author for pride and prejudice book?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:Who was the author for pride and prejudice book?\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: Who was the author for pride and prejudice book?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q170583 p:P50 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P50 ?x1 . }}\nThought:Executing the obtained SPARQL query. \n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q170583 p:P50 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P50 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q36322'}}]\nThought:The label for the returned entity needs to be detected.\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q36322]\n\nObservation: ['Jane Austen']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [Jane Austen]\n\nAssistant Response: Jane Austen is the author of the book Pride and prejudice."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is the director tv series alice in borderland?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:Who is the director tv series alice in borderland?\n\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: Who is the director tv series alice in borderland?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q103967305 p:P57 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P57 ?x1 . }}\nThought:Running the SPARQL query to get the answer.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q103967305 p:P57 ?x2 . ?x2 ps:P57 ?x1 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q7497770'}}]\nThought:Got the answer in terms of QID now getting the label from the QID\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: Q7497770\n\nObservation: Try again by passing values in a Python List format with comma separated values!\nThought:Got the answer in terms of QID now getting the label from the QIDNeed to pass a list\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q7497770]\n\nObservation: ['Shinsuke Sato']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [Shinsuke Sato]\n\nAssistant Response: Shinsuke Sato is the director of tv series alice in borderland."
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many filmed episodes of the dukes of hazzard are there?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tRunSparql",
        "One_Shot": "Question:How many filmed episodes of the dukes of hazzard are there?\n\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: How many filmed episodes of the dukes of hazzard are there?\n\nObservation: SELECT DISTINCT  (COUNT(DISTINCT ?x2) AS ?x1) WHERE {{ ?x2 wdt:P31 wd:Q15416 . ?x2 p:P179 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:P179 wd:Q1304408 . }}\nThought:trying to run the SPARQL query\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT (COUNT(DISTINCT ?x2) AS ?x1) WHERE {{ ?x2 wdt:P31 wd:Q15416 . ?x2 p:P179 ?x3 . ?x3 ps:P179 wd:Q1304408 . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'value': '0'}}]\nThought:The answer does not match Wikipedia, so the query is potentially incorrect. In the next step, the query should be fixed. \n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT DISTINCT ?x1 WHERE {{ wd:Q1304408 p:P1113 [ ps:P1113 ?x1 ] . }}\n\nObservation: [{{'P1113_8': {{'type': 'literal', 'value': '147', 'datatype': 'http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#decimal'}}}}]\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [147]\n\nAssistant Response: There are 147 filmed episodes of the Dukes of Hazzard American action comedy TV series."
    },
    {
        "Question": "What british sitcom is three's company an adaptation of?",
        "Dataset": "Compmix",
        "Action_Sequence": "\tWikiSearch\tGetWikidataID\tGenerateSparql\tRunSparql\tGetLabel",
        "One_Shot": "Question:What british sitcom is three's company an adaptation of?\n\n\nThought: Need to first generate the SPARQL query\n\nAction:GenerateSparql\n\nAction Input: What british sitcom is three's company an adaptation of?\n\nObservation: The possible reason is\n 1) The query is syntactically wrong\n\nThought:The above tool GenerateSparql did not return any query. There must be another way to construct the query by using P144: based on property.\n\nAction:RunSparql\n\nAction Input: SELECT ?x1  WHERE {{ wd:Q245996 wdt:P144 ?x1. }}\n\nObservation: {{'value': 'http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q2265954'}}\nThought:The responses are QID’s. To get the natural language responses, they need to be converted to labels. Now will get the Label\n\nAction:GetLabel\n\nAction Input: [Q2265954]\n\nObservation: ['Man About the House']\nFinal Answer: Wikidata_Answer: [Man About the House]\n\nAssistant Response: Man About the House is british sitcom three's company adaption of."
    }
]